<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on carminedestefano</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on carminedestefano</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Temesvar Code: Conspiring as an Art</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/code-temesvar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/code-temesvar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I read Il Codice Temesvar by Umberto Eco, one of my favorite authors and a renowned expert on conspiracy theories. Eco dedicated much of his work to dissecting the mechanisms behind conspiracies and their irresistible allure. In this particular book, he explores how conspiracy theories are born from esoteric interpretations of art, crafting a narrative around hidden messages and secret meanings supposedly encoded in Leonardo da Vinci’s Last Supper.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Email, Why Are You Still Here?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dear-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dear-email/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every time I write yet another email, I can’t help but wonder: why are we still doing this? In a world full of shiny chat apps and AI-powered tools, why do we keep clinging to emails? Are they a relic, or just a habit we can’t shake—like the stubborn QWERTY keyboard?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Emails are far from perfect. For some, they’re a polite way to avoid real-time interaction—a sort of formal “bubble” where you can pretend to be too busy to reply immediately. For others, they’re little more than a digital wasteland of spam and notifications. And then there are those people who treat emails like emergency texts, demanding immediate attention with bold subject lines and exclamation marks. The result? Chaos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
