<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>carminedestefano</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on carminedestefano</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 18:05:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 18:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m Carmine De Stefano, a curious soul who spends most of his time working on a computer. Born in 1997 in Potenza, I’ve been living in Turin for a few years now. I’m passionate about reading all kinds of books and writing short poems.&#xA;I’m not a fan of pointless labels or plot holes. In my free time, you’ll often find me exploring museums, strolling through parks, or soaking in the quiet beauty of dimly lit churches. The rest of the time, I’m chasing my endless curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Email, Why Are You Still Here?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every time I write yet another email, I can’t help but wonder: why are we still doing this? In a world full of shiny chat apps and AI-powered tools, why do we keep clinging to emails? Are they a relic, or just a habit we can’t shake—like the stubborn QWERTY keyboard?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Emails are far from perfect. For some, they’re a polite way to avoid real-time interaction—a sort of formal “bubble” where you can pretend to be too busy to reply immediately. For others, they’re little more than a digital wasteland of spam and notifications. And then there are those people who treat emails like emergency texts, demanding immediate attention with bold subject lines and exclamation marks. The result? Chaos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
